<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on RepairRabbit</title>
    <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on RepairRabbit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 17:06:56 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Biggest Error In Your Repair Business</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/the-biggest-error-in-your-repair-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 10:52:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/the-biggest-error-in-your-repair-business/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about the biggest and the most dangerous error in your repair business. And you know what? you&amp;rsquo;re totally unaware of it!
So, let&amp;rsquo;s get started. There are lots of repair businesses in the market who are constantly working hard to enhance their business but unfortunately, many of them fail! This is just because of some mistakes they ignore.
I think you&amp;rsquo;ve heard this before - &amp;ldquo;Stop chasing the money and start chasing the passion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Management Software For Repair Businesses</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/the-best-management-software-for-repair-businesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 10:40:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/the-best-management-software-for-repair-businesses/</guid>
      <description>These days, there are many repair businesses in the market. Everyone wants to turn their business into a brand. Well, every business can&amp;rsquo;t do this. Let&amp;rsquo;s assume, you&amp;rsquo;ve invested a huge amount of capital and started a repair business providing repair services of different appliances, vehicles, phones, and other electronic products. And you&amp;rsquo;re getting good business at the initial stage. But, after experiencing your services, no one comes back for your assistance!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Important Points That Every Repair Business Owner Should Keep In Mind</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/4-things-that-every-repair-business-owner-should-keep-in-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 15:08:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/4-things-that-every-repair-business-owner-should-keep-in-mind/</guid>
      <description>There are many repair businesses trying to hold their place in the market by offering different schemes, discounts, etc. But, if you want to grow your business on a decent speed, you need to know the basics work according to a plan. People think that investing a huge amount of capital is enough for them but, you need to invest the amount on proper resources which can guarantee you success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking Forward To Start A Repair Business? Here Are Some Tips &amp; Tricks For You.</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/looking-forward-to-start-a-new-repair-business-here-are-some-tips-and-tricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 12:16:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/looking-forward-to-start-a-new-repair-business-here-are-some-tips-and-tricks/</guid>
      <description>Starting a repair business is a great way to get your feet wet as an entrepreneur. You do not need to invest a huge amount at the initial stage of your business but as it grows, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to add more technicians, area for your service station, inventory, etc. You need proper management and organization for providing the best services. As in today&amp;rsquo;s market, you need to stand out from all others if you want to survive in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is How Using A Management Software Will Help You</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/this-is-how-using-a-management-software-will-help-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 16:55:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/this-is-how-using-a-management-software-will-help-you/</guid>
      <description>In today’s competitive market, there are lots of repair business providing the same kind of services. But everyone doesn’t stand out. The one who provides the best prices with quality services can be really successful in keeping the sales cycle going.
Do you know what converts the customers into Fans? Simple, quality of services does it for your company. Quality services help you to create a good reputation along with building brand loyal customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Major Mistakes That All The Repair Businesses Should Avoid</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/major-mistakes-that-all-the-repair-businesses-should-avoid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 15:22:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/major-mistakes-that-all-the-repair-businesses-should-avoid/</guid>
      <description>When you’re into a repair business, there are lots of components and departments to supervise. For e.g. - Customer data, Employee Data, Financial accounts, Stock management, Appointments, Customer feedback section, and so on. And you cannot afford any major error in these areas.
Business having multiple branches usually becomes the victim of mismanagement. It leads to disastrous results and sometimes a business has to shut doors. To survive in today’s market you have to put your 100% efforts in organizing the processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Retain Customers And Earn Brand Loyalty?</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/how-to-retain-customers-and-earn-brand-loyaly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 10:54:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/how-to-retain-customers-and-earn-brand-loyaly/</guid>
      <description>Nowadays businesses need to survive as people have invested a huge amount as a capital. Customer is king and businesses have to serve them the best to gain satisfaction. If your customer is not satisfied with your services you will not be able to get business from them again. This is a simple fact, right? But businesses still make mistakes in the organization, planning, and other factors which lead to revenue loss and poor customer satisfaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Amazing Tips To Improve Organisation And Increase Revenue Of Your Repair Business</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/4-amazing-tips-to-improve-organisation-and-increase-sales-of-your-repair-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 15:52:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/4-amazing-tips-to-improve-organisation-and-increase-sales-of-your-repair-business/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to running a repair business, it&amp;rsquo;s quite necessary to give proper attention to each and every factor like appointments, customers&#39; data, employees&#39; data, tickets, etc. Thus it becomes difficult to organize the work properly. Sometimes stress leads to mismanagement and it ultimately causes revenue loss. Thus, it is quite essential to look after all the factors equally and manage them in one place.
Some useful tips for all the repair businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effects Of Bad Scheduling On Your Repair Business</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/effects-of-bad-scheduling-on-your-repair-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 16:01:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/effects-of-bad-scheduling-on-your-repair-business/</guid>
      <description>Nowadays cell phones are a very important part of everyone&amp;rsquo;s life, people can hardly survive without their cell phones for a single day as they are the most used medium of communication with the help of the internet, social media, etc. And businesses have to take care of the requirement of each and every customer. They will demand to complete the repair of their device as soon as possible or some of them will demand to complete the repair work on the spot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Is Digitalized Management System Better Than Traditional Ones?</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/how-is-digitalized-management-system-better-than-traditional-ones/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 11:46:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/how-is-digitalized-management-system-better-than-traditional-ones/</guid>
      <description>There are many different methods that organizations follow for management. There are many traditional methods too but a business needs to identify the best method for the proper management.
For repair businesses, it&amp;rsquo;s quite difficult to manage workflow and other factors like inventory, customers&#39; data, employee management, etc. Thus having a proper management setup which helps you to develop the organization is crucial. There are still many businesses using traditional methods for management of the business like maintaining books for accounting, difficult processes for invoices, appointments, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improve Customer Services By Adopting Digitalized Management System.</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/improve-cutomer-services-by-adopting-digitalized-management-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 13:32:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/improve-cutomer-services-by-adopting-digitalized-management-system/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s competitive market, there are lots of repair business providing the same kind of services. But everyone doesn&amp;rsquo;t stand out. The one who provides the best prices with quality services can be really successful in keeping the sales cycle going.
Do you know what converts the customers into Fans? Simple, quality of services does it for your company. Quality services help you to create a good reputation along with building brand loyal customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Avoid Mismanagement And Its Disastrous Effects?</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/how-to-avoid-mismanagement-and-its-disastrous-effects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 14:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/how-to-avoid-mismanagement-and-its-disastrous-effects/</guid>
      <description>There are many strategies and different ways to avoid mismanagement and its effects on your repair business. Strategies can be prepared easily but they&amp;rsquo;re really difficult to work on when your organization is suffering from problems like mismanagement. Nowadays when there is a huge work list and high workload, it becomes more difficult for a business owner to find out solutions for the day-to-day problems. But nowadays businesses are having a lot many options for handling and supervising their business online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effects of Mismanagement On A Repair Business</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/effects-of-mismanagement-on-a-repair-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 15:37:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/effects-of-mismanagement-on-a-repair-business/</guid>
      <description>Mismanagement, less organized processes, lack of planning, etc. together lead to many disadvantages. Sometimes due to mismanagement organization has to suffer through major revenue loss. And in today&amp;rsquo;s competitive market, companies cannot afford revenue loses. Thus, it&amp;rsquo;s quite necessary to work according to roadmaps and achievable plans.
As we disscussed about mismanagement in a repair businesspreviously, it&amp;rsquo;s time to know its effects. Reduced Productivity If employers fail to notice or act upon, occasions where employees are failing to meet performance expectations, the situation could be worst and reduce levels of productivity across the workforce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mismanagement In A Repair Business And Its Causes</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/mismanagement-in-a-repair-business-and-its-causes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 12:14:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/mismanagement-in-a-repair-business-and-its-causes/</guid>
      <description>When you&amp;rsquo;re into a repair business, there are lots of components and departments to supervise. For eg - Customer data, Employee Data, Financial accounts, Stock management, Appointments, Customer feedback section, and so on. And you cannot afford any major error in these areas.
Business having multiple branches usually becomes the victim of mismanagement. It leads to disastrous results and sometimes a business has to shut doors. To survive in today&amp;rsquo;s market you have to put your 100% efforts in organizing the processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How does Online Appointment Scheduling Leads to Advancement of a Repair Business?</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/how-does-online-appointment-scheduling-leads-to-advancement-of-a-repair-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 12:33:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/how-does-online-appointment-scheduling-leads-to-advancement-of-a-repair-business/</guid>
      <description>NNowadays medical centers, hair salons, sports clubs, and many more businesses are offering their customers online appointments. Customers will like convenient services, and they would love it if they have 24/7 access, whether that’s booking a hotel room or scheduling an oil change. And thus repair businesses are also adopting the Digitalized scheduling system. This is because people are usually active on the internet whether on mobile phones, tablet or their computers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Role of Appointments in a Repair Businesses</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/role-of-appointments-in-a-repair-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 12:52:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/role-of-appointments-in-a-repair-business/</guid>
      <description>In the repair business, there are multiple factors to look after such as inventory, invoices, tickets, appointments, etc. One of these factors &amp;ldquo;Appointments&amp;rdquo; play an important role in the development of repair businesses.
Let&amp;rsquo;s know how? In a repair shop, there are many devices under repair and many are to come. Sometimes customers want their devices to be repaired on the spot or on a specific time. And if you haven&amp;rsquo;t adopted the appointment system, it becomes difficult to manage all the customers at a time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Stop Solution For Repair Businesses</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/one-stop-solution-for-repair-businesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 15:43:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/one-stop-solution-for-repair-businesses/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s market, a repair business company needs to manage multiple factors to organize the business properly. For e.g. - A repair business owner has to look after the data of his employees, customers, stock, repairs, finances, etc. Business having multiple branches usually face problems. And sometimes it becomes difficult to keep an eye on each factor.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry RepairRabbit is here to help! RepairRabbit will act as a one-stop solution for all the repair businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integration Of RepairRabbit With Other Softwares</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/integration-of-repairrabbit-with-other-softwares/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 12:09:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/integration-of-repairrabbit-with-other-softwares/</guid>
      <description>Data management is an important factor for every business. Many systems fail to protect your data from destruction! But, we have something that will help you to maintain data and to keep it safe and secure at a place.
Now, does the thought of data loss hinder you to use RepairRabbit? We value your concern. Thus, We have built RepairRabbit in a way where you don&amp;rsquo;t really need to worry about your existing data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everthing You Need to Know About RepairRabbit API</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/everthing-you-need-to-know-about-repairrabbit-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 16:01:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/everthing-you-need-to-know-about-repairrabbit-api/</guid>
      <description>What is RepairRabbit API? An application programming interface (API) is an overloaded word. In general terms, it is a set of defined methods and protocols to communicate with different components of the software. It allows software to communicate with other software/applications. For example:- Yelp shows restaurants on Google Map. At that time Yelp communicated with Google map through the API by passing restaurant details to Google map. So that Google can plot restaurants as pins on their map.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RepairRabbit API Is Out Now!</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/repairrabbit-api-is-out-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 12:07:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/repairrabbit-api-is-out-now/</guid>
      <description>APIs play an important role in managing, transferring your data, and working on other manual processes. They also help you coordinate with other systems. And in a repair business, there are multiple factors to look after like - tickets, appointments, customer data, employee data, etc. Thus we&amp;rsquo;ve been working on RepairRabbit API since long and finally, it has been launched!
Let&amp;rsquo;s see how it will be useful for your repair business   It&amp;rsquo;s now easy to integrate with other softwares for securing and transferring your data to the RepairRabbit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Big Feature Coming Soon - RepairRabbit API</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/new-big-feature-coming-soon-repairrabbit-apis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 19:24:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/new-big-feature-coming-soon-repairrabbit-apis/</guid>
      <description>APIs play an important role in managing, transferring your data, and working on other manual processes right? They also help you coordinate with other systems. And in a repair business, there are multiple factors to look after like - tickets, appointments, customer data, employee data, etc.
RepairRabbit is such a platform where you can manage your inventory, customer database, employee information, etc. And with ReapirRabbit API you will be able to move the data from one system to another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Daily, Weekly And Monthly Revenue Report Using RepiarRabbit</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/get-daily-weekly-and-monthly-revenue-report-using-repiarrabbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 12:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/get-daily-weekly-and-monthly-revenue-report-using-repiarrabbit/</guid>
      <description>By applying custom range you can find out the revenue amount of selected dates. Just select the dates, store, and click the search button and get access over the total earning amount.
Check total revenue of selected days by applying filters. Revenue can be directly checked from the dashboard with the help of system shortcuts. There is less room for errors as transactions are automatically saved as per the invoices generated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Access on Business Activities With RepairRabbit Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/quick-access-on-business-activities-with-repairrabbit-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 12:21:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/quick-access-on-business-activities-with-repairrabbit-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Frustrated with lengthy software processes? Tired of following the same boring format? Then there is good news for you!! RepairRabbit offers easy to use shortcuts for every important task with just one click access to save your valuable time.
Book an appointment directly on just a click from the dashboard. Repair ticket and invoice are the core components of every repair business and it is a lengthy &amp;amp; time-consuming process as it includes very minute details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Employee Management</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/easy-employee-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 17:24:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/easy-employee-management/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s quite difficult to keep records of your employees working in multiple stores. There are too many regulations and numbers to keep track of. RepairRabbit will help you to reduce the paperwork and maintain data of employees of multiple stores at a place.
Want to keep a record of repairs done by an employee? RepairRabbit will make it possible for you. Assign work to your employees and check work done by them accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plan Your Work With RepairRabbit Calendar</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/plan-your-work-with-repairrabbit-calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 18:28:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/plan-your-work-with-repairrabbit-calendar/</guid>
      <description>With RepairRabbit calendar its easy to plan work schedule for booked appointments. It also helps you to verify appointment status. Assign work to your employees with individual date and time. Organize and track important tasks. Checking employee&amp;rsquo;s availability for task distribution becomes easy. As you have details about the employees who are on leave, you can distribute work accordingly to avoid delay in the work.
Core Advantages 1 Increase work flow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Businesses Who Can Take Advantage Of RepairRabbit Software</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/businesses-who-can-take-advantage-of-repairrabbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 17:33:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/businesses-who-can-take-advantage-of-repairrabbit/</guid>
      <description>List of business who can take advantage of RepairRabbit software  Phone repair business Laptop repair business Accessories repair business Electronic devices repair business Auto/Vehicle repair business Jewelry repair business Watch repair business Camera repair business Drone repair business Musical instrument repair business General repair business  All kind of repair businesses can take advantage of RepairRabbit software and grow their business
Contact usfor pricing &amp;amp; purchase information or try RepairRabbit free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Ticket in RepairRabbit?</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/what-is-ticket-in-repairrabbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 13:48:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/what-is-ticket-in-repairrabbit/</guid>
      <description>Tickets The main organ of a repair shop is its ticketing system. Repair ticket is a job sheet, the tickets will show you exactly what you need, when you need it, from any device. The lightweight workflow will gently remind you of the next task without getting in your way or slowing you down. Maintaining a record of repair tickets can be helpful in the future. You can check daily, weekly &amp;amp; monthly repair tickets easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction To RepairRabbit</title>
      <link>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/introduction-to-repairrabbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 18:23:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dev-docs.repairrabbit.co/blog/introduction-to-repairrabbit/</guid>
      <description>RepairRabbit is a self-hosted software that offers automation to your repair business.
RepairRabbit allows you to monitor multiple repair stores&#39; operation and services. It also helps in managing tickets, customer records, and their progress.
RepairRabbit helps you to minimize your paperwork in the repair business. We are serving different industries to minimize their workload and time to maximize their productivity.
Features of RepairRabbit Dashboard Basically Dashboard means report or progress report.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
