<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>feature on RepairRabbit</title><link>https://www.repairrabbit.co/tags/feature/</link><description>Recent content in feature on RepairRabbit</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 12:07:03 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.repairrabbit.co/tags/feature/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>RepairRabbit API Is Out Now!</title><link>https://www.repairrabbit.co/blog/repairrabbit-api-is-out-now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 12:07:03 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://www.repairrabbit.co/blog/repairrabbit-api-is-out-now/</guid><description>APIs play an important role in managing, transferring your data, and working on other manual processes. They also help you coordinate with other systems. And in a repair business, there are multiple factors to look after like - tickets, appointments, customer data, employee data, etc. Thus we&amp;rsquo;ve been working on RepairRabbit API since long and finally, it has been launched!
Let&amp;rsquo;s see how it will be useful for your repair business It&amp;rsquo;s now easy to integrate with other softwares for securing and transferring your data to the RepairRabbit.</description></item><item><title>New Big Feature Coming Soon - RepairRabbit API</title><link>https://www.repairrabbit.co/blog/new-big-feature-coming-soon-repairrabbit-apis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 19:24:07 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://www.repairrabbit.co/blog/new-big-feature-coming-soon-repairrabbit-apis/</guid><description>APIs play an important role in managing, transferring your data, and working on other manual processes right? They also help you coordinate with other systems. And in a repair business, there are multiple factors to look after like - tickets, appointments, customer data, employee data, etc.
RepairRabbit is such a platform where you can manage your inventory, customer database, employee information, etc. And with ReapirRabbit API you will be able to move the data from one system to another.</description></item></channel></rss>